question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of &quot;Doomhammer&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Undertale&quot;, the main character of the game is Sans.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
